<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Play_report on Hairy Thinker</title>
    <link>http://hairythinker.com/tags/play_report/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Play_report on Hairy Thinker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 May 2015 00:11:48 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://hairythinker.com/tags/play_report/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Play Report: Twilight Imperium - 24&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; May 2015</title>
      <link>http://hairythinker.com/games/2015/05/play-report-twilight-imperium-24-may/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2015 00:11:48 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://hairythinker.com/games/2015/05/play-report-twilight-imperium-24-may/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;personal-log-of-admiral-waaz-commander-of-the-yssaril-military:6ca929029d3fe5aec286264d3075417d&#34;&gt;Personal Log of Admiral Waaz, Commander of the Yssaril Military&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve just landed ground troops in the capital. It&amp;rsquo;s a bold move and I&amp;rsquo;m
worried that I&amp;rsquo;ve made my play for the capital system of Mecatol Rex too early.
My twin Dreadnought class ships were two systems away from the capital; too far
away to support the invasion force. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;m a fool for revealing my
intentions this early? But the opportunity was there! I had to take it! The
Sardakk N&amp;rsquo;orr had Dreadnoughts two systems away from the capital as well and
intelligence from our spies revealed that their admiral had ordered his ships
to
fly at flank speed, allowing them to reach the system before I could cope with
them. Thankfully, the Yssaril Tribes are a wily race and sabotaged the enemy
Dreadnoughts, buying us enough time to move our friendly Dreadnoughts into
position to defend the capital system. The Sardakk N&amp;rsquo;orr moved into the Mecatol
Rex system without their Dreadnoughts but their fleet damn near destroyed my
forces regardless. Had it not been for the courageous efforts of the Yssaril
engineers carrying out emergency repairs during the battle I shudder to think
of
the casualties we could have incurred. We&amp;rsquo;ve kept the system this time; I just
hope we can hold it until the mission is finished.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;time-passes:6ca929029d3fe5aec286264d3075417d&#34;&gt;Time passes&amp;hellip;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve made significant technology advances but I&amp;rsquo;ve still not yet
completed my objective. In the intervening time the Sardakk N&amp;rsquo;orr have readied
a huge invasion fleet and both the Universities of Jol-Nar and the diplomatic
Xxcha Kingdom have increased their presence in the systems adjacent to Mecatol
Rex. The Mentak Coalition, a race of deceitful pirates, have cut off the supply
lines to Mecatol Rex, a situation made worse by Mecatol Rex recently being
declared a holy planet on which industry is prohibited. My troops stationed
there are dug in deep, but reinforcing the system is no longer an option.
Outraged by my treatment of the Sardakk N&amp;rsquo;orr, the Emirates of Hacan launched a
successful assault on a system containing two economically important Yssaril
controlled planets. They are currently blockading the space dock in that
system,
preventing the production of new Yssaril ships. What is worse, of course, is
that the Hacan now have a fleet of Dreadnoughts and Cruisers in flight range of
the planet on which I was born and raised. I&amp;rsquo;m having to decide whether to
commit resources to complete my objective &lt;em&gt;or&lt;/em&gt; to protect the plant on which my
family live; it&amp;rsquo;s a decision I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t wish upon my worse enemy. I just need
to
maintain control of Mecatol Rex for a little longer, but all of these enemy
fleets are making me nervous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;a-new-emperor-is-soon-to-take-the-imperial-throne:6ca929029d3fe5aec286264d3075417d&#34;&gt;A new emperor is soon to take the imperial throne&amp;hellip;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We did it! We bloody well did it! Our scientists finally finished the work they
needed to do on Mecatol Rex; whatever we need that research for, it better be
worth it. It couldn&amp;rsquo;t have happened sooner enough; the Sardakk N&amp;rsquo;orr armada was
so close to Mecatol Rex that from the capital all you could see in the sky was
menacing metal. Our fleet left the system just in time and were able to make it
back into friendlier systems to reclaim terretories lost to the Hacan and
defend our race&amp;rsquo;s ancestral home planets. With my primary objective completed,
I was tasked with maintaining the Yssaril borders while final efforts to claim
the imperial thone were enacted. We were too late. The piratical Mentak
Coalition made a ruthless push to claim the home planets of the Xxcha Kingdom,
winning them enough influence to take the throne. I can&amp;rsquo;t hide my
disappointment about the lack of a Yssaril emperor, but I&amp;rsquo;m sure the Mentak
will be suitable leaders. My only wish is for peace to be restored to this
troubled galaxy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>